Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you!
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem!
Then I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
We'll live in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We'll live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
But we don't wanna live ordinary life.
But we have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
What's wrong, huh?
You've had that brooding look
on your face for a while.
Yeah, I guess I hoped I
was dreaming. About what?
This may sound crazy, but it
seems to me we're not even moving.
You feel that?
Now that you mention it, the sail doesn't
appear to be catching any wind at all.
No! We're screwed!
We've entered the Calm Belt!
The Clam Belt? What's that?
Calm Belt!
A part of the sea where
nothing moves a muscle!
So there's muscles and clams? No!
What was that, an earthquake?
A good trick since we're at sea.
All of this chit-chat isn't
going to get us out of here.
Fold the sails and start paddling now.
We have to get back on course.
You can count on me. Don't panic.
And besides, this is a sailboat.
Why do we need to paddle?
True.
And why would we go through the trouble of
doubling back when the
Marines are waiting for us?
Look, there's no time to argue.
Just shut up and do as I say.
At least it's nice and quiet here.
Oh, fine.
If I need to explain it to you, I will.
In our haste to escape from the Marines,
we ended up going too far south and now
we're off course and stuck out here!
So we entered the Grand Line?
Woo-hoo-hoo!
If we were at the Grand Line, you think
I'd waste my time explaining this?!
Now look!
The Grand Line is sandwiched in the middle
between these two green
areas you see here,
you understand?
These areas, just as they're labeled,
are what's called the Calm Belt.
That's where we are.
Nobody knows why, but inside the Calm
Belt, there's no wind and no current.
It's like a void where
everything's stagnant.
Given that sailboats move by catching
winds, this is more than a dangerous region.
It can be fatal, get it?
Nope, but it sounds like
we're in big trouble.
Good, you retained more
than I thought you would.
So this is what that geezer meant
when he said it was dangerous.
Well, that explains why we haven't
gotten a single gust of wind.
How are we gonna get out of
this if our ship can't move?
Maybe the wind will start blowing again.
Wind never blows in the calm belt.
And that's not all.
There's another good reason that
people call this area dangerous.
It's infested with blood.
What was that?
Sea monsters!
They're gigantic!
The Calm Belt is also
home to the Sea Kings.
It's their main place for breeding.
They're the biggest reason
people can't cross the Calm Belt.
Any idea how we get out of this?
We don't want to give them any
reason to stick around or eat us.
Once they're gone, we'll paddle back.
Got it?
You call that a plan?
Shut up!
Sorry.
That didn't improve anything!
It sounds like it's gonna!
Please yourselves, I think
this behemoth's gonna sneeze!
Well, at least we're back
on our original course.
According to the map, we should be
spotting the red line anytime now.
Wow, we're almost there,
the Grand Line at last!
Isn't this exciting?
We're finally going! We did it! We did it!
Cut it out! Sorry.
Zoro!
You must be right.
Is the path to the Grand Line really as
perilous as it's drawn here? Stop that!
Take a look.
I'm familiar with the rumors
and these drawings confirm it.
As unimaginable as it may seem, the
entrance to the Grand Line is a mountain.
So what, did we crash into it?
You gotta be kidding.
I didn't believe it, but the map's clear.
The mountain appears to be
riddled with small canals,
so we might have to go up and over it.
Sounds like fun.
What are you talking about?
Even if there are canals or whatever,
a ship can't climb up a mountain.
Well, the map says otherwise.
That's right, and if Nami thinks
something can be done, then it can't.
Got that?
Yeah, but remember, that map was stolen
from Buggy the Clown, so can we trust if...
In case no one noticed,
the rudder's stuck.
A little help over here be nice Sanji,
would you please give Usopp a hand?
I can't think with all his shouting
It's happening right away, Nami!
Okay.
Uh, does this current seem
unusually strong to anyone else?
Usopp, what did you just say?
I asked if any of you noticed the
insane strength of this current.
The current?
That must be... What is it?
The canals do go up the
mountain. Oh, come on.
How could that possibly work?
Look right here.
You see?
The guiding light was directing us
toward this spot on the red line.
Notice how it's labeled
here, Reverse Mountain.
Hello?
Little help over here, thank you!
These green lines represent
canals, or artificial waterways.
If major currents from all four
oceans flow toward this mountain,
what do you think's gonna happen?
The currents would force
water up these canals,
collide at the top, and then flow
straight down into the Grand Line.
Now, Reverse Mountain is a winter
mountain, so it's cold, right?
That means any surface
currents that don't flow
up the canal will be
forced down as they cool.
Anything riding those currents
would be pulled down as well.
If we screw up and miss
the entrance to the canal,
the Going Mary will be
carried straight into
the Red Line's rock base
and likely be destroyed.
Ship and crew would be sucked
to the bottom of the sea.
Understand?
Yeah.
Basically, it's a mystery mountain.
No, that's not my point at all.
Anyway,
since we're positioned on this current,
we shouldn't run into any problems
getting to the summit of Reverse Mountain.
Only thing that would hurt us now is if
something went wrong with the rudder.
Nami, you're a genius!
Call me a skeptic, but ships
do not climb mountains.
Well, I've heard a few stories.
Stories about the Mystery Mountain? No,
what I have heard is that more
than half the people who try
to make it to the Grand Line
die before they even get there.
Whatever we find, it
isn't going to be easy.
Sanji, could you get the sail?
Anything for you, Nami! Luffy, help me!
Got it!
Hey!
I can see the mystery mountain!
That's insanely huge!
Wow! Awesome!
It's bigger than I thought!
I can't see the top!
It's taller than the clouds!
We're getting sucked in!
Hold the rudder steady!
We're on it!
Nami!
Where's that entrance
you were talking about?
If we keep this heading, we're
going to crash into the rocks!
There's a crack in that cliff.
That must be it.
Nami!
Give us a direction!
Keep bearing straight ahead!
You can't be serious! Trust me!
Have we made it?
Is that the canal entrance?
More than likely.
I've got to be dreaming.
It's impossible.
The ocean really is
flowing up the mountain.
We have to make our way through
those water gates just right.
Or we'll crash into the red
line and be smashed to pieces.
We're drifting off course.
Gotta go more to the right.
Go right.
Go in starboard.
Come on, now!
Put your back into it!
The runner!
Gum-Gum balloon!
Loopy!
Grab a hold!
We made it!
Now it's just a straight
shot to the summit!
Wow, great view!
Whoa!
Look how high we are!
We're in the clouds!
This is insane!
We're not in the clouds, we're above them!
It's amazing! We've done it!
We've reached the summit!
Woohoo!
I can see it!
This is the greatest
sea in the whole world!
The Grand Lie!
Somewhere out there, the One Piece
is waiting, and we're gonna find it!
Let's go!
Did you guys just hear something?
It was probably just the wind!
At this speed, everything
sounds distorted!
What was that?
Nami!
I see a mountain up ahead!
What? That's impossible!
But it's right there!
I can see it!
Who cares? Go!
After we pass the twin caves up ahead,
there should be nothing but ocean!
It's a black wall!
No, it's not!
Then what is it?
It's a whale!
What are we going to do?
Should we fight?
Idiots, how are we supposed
to fight a hundred-ton whale?
Do something!
Our path is blocked!
How do we escape? Calm down.
If this creature looks like a giant wall
to us, We must be a speck! That's right!
It's highly possible that this thing
isn't even aware that we're here!
We'll run right into it
unless we change course!
Look!
We can get by on the left!
Port!
Port to port!
The rudder's broken!
Do something!
Anything! Wait! I know!
This'll work! It has to!
Hey!
Luffy, what are you doing?
This is pointless!
The ship's not going to turn!
Dammit!
Don't give up!
Is this the end?
The cannon!
Done.
Hey, that was my special scene!
Damn!
Let's get out of here
before it's too late!
Don't mind telling me
what the heck is going on!
It's so big that the cannonball
didn't even make it flinch!
That or his reaction time's really slow!
Who cares?
At least we're alive!
My ears!
Just battle!
I have to get away from here!
Luffy?
You think you can break my special seat?
Get away with it!
Take this!
You moron!
I'm not through with you!
There's a lot more with it!
Shut up before you kill us!
Please, no!
I am not gonna die!
Oh, man.
Everyone's been swallowed whole.
Hey, you!
Can you hear me?
Spit him out!
I want my friend! Damn you!
Where do you think
you're going, you jerk?!
You give them back right now, you whale!
Listen, you big bone,
I'm not gonna ask again!
Stop sinking, I mean it!
My friends and me are on
an important adventure!
I can't lose them!
Give them back!
So what do you think I don't know what
to think is this even real because
I know exactly what I saw and what I
felt we were swallowed by the whale?
Is this a dream?
Yeah, I'd say that's a fair guess.
Then what's with this island
and the house? Illusions.
Um, that looks like...
A Great Game Squad!
Looks like someone's home.
Let's hope it's a person.
I've had it.
Let's go.
Giant squids, guys with harpoons.
And where is Luffy?
Yeah, where is he?
I don't know much about whales,
but since when do they have
doors and lighted hallways?
A ship?
We should fire a cannon there! Now!
No, hold on a sec.
Someone's coming out.
I wrote you a love song
to let you know that
I want to be with you
till the end of time.
Even when the sparkles fade in doubts
invade our ones so trusting might.
I promise you that I will stay,
we'll find a way to look
through the cloudy skies.
We built a castle of sand.
And now we're watching it wash away.
It doesn't have to end.
We'll start again.
This time round we'll
build a stronger love.
Oh, you've got me heart and soul.
I just wanna hold you and not let go.
You know that I'll be with
you till the end of time.
Oh, you've got me heart and soul.